================= Logging started at 4/3/2019 09:56:21 ==================
Created release folders
Creating updated setup image...
Setting product version...
Setting package code...
Updating application files...
ISDEV : warning -6547: The file 'pointage.ps1' already exists in the setup. Please modify the existing file instead of inserting a new one otherwise this file may not uninstall properly.
Updating registry entries...
Performing Upgrading and Patching Validation
Val0003:	This setup will perform a MINOR upgrade of the referenced previous setup	c:\users\shebbir\onedrive - cls - collecte localisation satellites\scripts\powershell\adp\v2\v02.02\adp pointage assist v02.02 p1\baseimage\adp pointage assist v02.02.msi
Creating Patch Configuration Properties...
Building MsiPatchMetadata table
Creating Patch...
Validating MSI input file...
Table: Properties
Table: ImageFamilies
Table: UpgradedImages
Table: TargetImages
Table: UpgradedFilesToIgnore
Table: ExternalFiles
Table: TargetFiles_OptionalData
Table: FamilyFileRanges
Table: UpgradedFiles_OptionalData
Creating file patches...
Family00
Creating cabinet file...
Cleaning up temporary files...
Creating Update Launcher
Copying base files to release location
Preparing the upgraded image
Preparing setup.ini
Instrumenting package for localization
Saving setup.ini
Saving Update Launcher
The patch creation process has completed with:  0 Errors and 1 Warnings.
================= Logging stopped at 4/3/2019 09:56:23 ==================
Log file has been created: <file:C:\Users\shebbir\OneDrive - CLS - Collecte Localisation Satellites\Scripts\Powershell\ADP\V2\V02.02\ADP POINTAGE ASSIST V02.02 P1\Interm\4-3-2019 09-56-21.txt>

